Women's Building; Records apap292
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Administrative File, 1971-2000, Undated; 1; 10 cubic ft.
  - Deposit Records - Key Bank, 1995-1996 (Box 7 (1-Administrative File), Folder 70)
  - Deposit Records - TrustCo, 1995-1996 (Box 7 (1-Administrative File), Folder 71)
  - Gail Dieter - Accounts Payable, 1995-1996 (Box 7 (1-Administrative File), Folder 72)
  - Gail Dieter - Tax Documents, priority, 1995-1996 (Box 7 (1-Administrative File), Folder 73)
  - Donation, 1995 (Box 7 (1-Administrative File), Folder 74)
  - Finance Committee, 1995-1996 (Box 7 (1-Administrative File), Folder 75)
  - Financial Statements Fiscal Year, 1995 (Box 7 (1-Administrative File), Folder 76)
  - Fundraiser's: Golf, 1995 (Box 8 (1-Administrative File), Folder 1)
  - Fundraising - Response to Winnie DeLoayza letter, 1995 (Box 8 (1-Administrative File), Folder 2)
  - Historical - Lay-Off of Executive Director Article, 1995-1996 (Box 8 (1-Administrative File), Folder 3)
  - Rent Invoices Received, 1995-1996 (Box 8 (1-Administrative File), Folder 4)
  - Insurance, Disability, Natural Home Ownership Strategy, 1995-1996 (Box 8 (1-Administrative File), Folder 5)
  - Landan - Emergency Coordinating Council Meeting (Fiscal Crisis), 1995 (Box 8 (1-Administrative File), Folder 6)
  - Membership, 1995-1996 (Box 8 (1-Administrative File), Folder 7)
  - Other Women's Centers, 1995-1997 (Box 8 (1-Administrative File), Folder 8)
  - Referral Log, 1995 (Box 8 (1-Administrative File), Folder 9)
  - Roof Repair Donations, 1995 (Box 8 (1-Administrative File), Folder 10)
  - SEFA, 1995-1996 (Box 8 (1-Administrative File), Folder 11)
  - SEFA - Donation List, 1995-1996 (Box 8 (1-Administrative File), Folder 12)
  - Tax Returns, 1995 (Box 8 (1-Administrative File), Folder 13)
  - Taxes, 1995-1996 (Box 8 (1-Administrative File), Folder 14)
  - Tides Foundation, 1995 (Box 8 (1-Administrative File), Folder 15)
  - Transition (financial crisis), 1995 (Box 8 (1-Administrative File), Folder 16)
  - United Way Schenectady, 1995-1996 (Box 8 (1-Administrative File), Folder 17)
  - Ad Manifests, 1996-1998 (Box 8 (1-Administrative File), Folder 18)
  - Art and Desire, 1996 (Box 8 (1-Administrative File), Folder 19)
  - Bank Statements - January, 1996-1997 (Box 8 (1-Administrative File), Folder 20)
  - Bank Statements - February, 1996-1997 (Box 8 (1-Administrative File), Folder 21)
  - Bank Statements - March, 1996-1997 (Box 8 (1-Administrative File), Folder 22)
  - Bank Statements - April, 1996-1997 (Box 8 (1-Administrative File), Folder 23)
  - Bank Statements - May, 1996-1997 (Box 8 (1-Administrative File), Folder 24)
  - Bank Statements - June, 1996-1997 (Box 8 (1-Administrative File), Folder 25)
  - Bank Statements - July, 1996-1997 (Box 8 (1-Administrative File), Folder 26)
  - Bank Statements - August, 1996-1997 (Box 8 (1-Administrative File), Folder 27)
  - Bank Statements - September, 1996-1997 (Box 8 (1-Administrative File), Folder 28)
  - Bank Statements - October, 1996-1997 (Box 8 (1-Administrative File), Folder 29)
  - Bank Statements - November, 1996-1997 (Box 8 (1-Administrative File), Folder 30)
  - Bank Statements - December, 1996-1997 (Box 8 (1-Administrative File), Folder 31)
  - Bank Statements (TrustCo) - January, 1996 (Box 8 (1-Administrative File), Folder 32)
  - Bank Statements (TrustCo)-February, 1996 (Box 8 (1-Administrative File), Folder 33)
  - Bank Statements (TrustCo) - March, 1996 (Box 8 (1-Administrative File), Folder 34)
  - Bank Statements (TrustCo) - April, 1996 (Box 8 (1-Administrative File), Folder 35)
  - Bank Statements (TrustCo) - May, 1996 (Box 8 (1-Administrative File), Folder 36)
  - Bank Statements (TrustCo) - June, 1996 (Box 8 (1-Administrative File), Folder 37)
  - Bank Statements (TrustCo) - September, 1996 (Box 8 (1-Administrative File), Folder 38)
  - Bills, 1996-1998 (Box 8 (1-Administrative File), Folder 39)
  - Combined Federal Campaign, 1996 (Box 8 (1-Administrative File), Folder 40)
  - Coordinating council, 1996-1997 (Box 8 (1-Administrative File), Folder 41)
  - Decentralization Grant - Drum Festival, 1996 (Box 8 (1-Administrative File), Folder 42)
  - Deposit Record, 1996-1997 (Box 8 (1-Administrative File), Folder 43)
  - Deposit Records - Key Bank, 1996-1997 (Box 8 (1-Administrative File), Folder 44)
  - Deposit Records - TrustCo - July, 1996 (Box 8 (1-Administrative File), Folder 45)
  - Deposit Records - TrustCo - August, 1996 (Box 8 (1-Administrative File), Folder 46)
  - Deposit Records - TrustCo - October, 1996 (Box 8 (1-Administrative File), Folder 47)
  - Deposit Records - TrustCo - November, 1996 (Box 8 (1-Administrative File), Folder 48)
  - Deposit Records - TrustCo - December, 1996 (Box 8 (1-Administrative File), Folder 49)
  - Gail Dieter - Treasurer Records, 1996-1997 (Box 8 (1-Administrative File), Folder 50)
  - Gail Dieter - Treasurer Records, 1996; 1998 (Box 8 (1-Administrative File), Folder 51)
  - Donor Sheets, 1996 (Box 8 (1-Administrative File), Folder 52)
  - Elword - Germaine Curtin, 1996 (Box 8 (1-Administrative File), Folder 53)
  - Grant Applications, 1996 (Box 8 (1-Administrative File), Folder 54)
  - Grant - Community Foundation for Women in Motion, 1996 (Box 8 (1-Administrative File), Folder 55)
  - Grants - Hewlett Packard, 1996 (Box 8 (1-Administrative File), Folder 56)
  - Historical - Response to Lay-Off Article, 1996 (Box 8 (1-Administrative File), Folder 57)
  - Major Donors, 1996-1997 (Box 8 (1-Administrative File), Folder 58)
  - Louise McNeilly, 1996-1997 (Box 8 (1-Administrative File), Folder 59)
  - Louise McNeilly - Advertising, 1996-1997 (Box 8 (1-Administrative File), Folder 60)
  - Louise McNeilly, 1996-1997 (Box 8 (1-Administrative File), Folder 61)
  - Louise McNeilly, 1996-1997 (Box 8 (1-Administrative File), Folder 62)
  - Louise McNeilly, 1996-1997 (Box 8 (1-Administrative File), Folder 63)
  - Louise McNeilly, 1996-1997 (Box 8 (1-Administrative File), Folder 64)
  - Louise McNeilly - Copies Billing Forums, 1996-1997 (Box 8 (1-Administrative File), Folder 65)
  - Louise McNeilly - Council of Community Services, 1996-1997 (Box 8 (1-Administrative File), Folder 66)
  - Louise McNeilly, 1996-1997 (Box 8 (1-Administrative File), Folder 67)
  - Louise McNeilly - Insurance Statements and Billings, Property, Casualty, and Liability, 1996-1997 (Box 8 (1-Administrative File), Folder 68)
  - Louise McNeilly, 1996-1997 (Box 8 (1-Administrative File), Folder 69)
  - Louise McNeilly, 1996-1997 (Box 8 (1-Administrative File), Folder 70)
  - Louise McNeilly, 1996 (Box 8 (1-Administrative File), Folder 71)
  - Louise McNeilly, 1995-1996 (Box 8 (1-Administrative File), Folder 72)
  - Louise McNeilly - Key Bank Mortgages, 1996-1997 (Box 9 (1-Administrative File), Folder 1)
  - Louise McNeilly, 1996-1997 (Box 9 (1-Administrative File), Folder 2)
  - Louise McNeilly - NYNEX, 1996-1997 (Box 9 (1-Administrative File), Folder 3)
  - Louise McNeilly - Office Max, 1996-1997 (Box 9 (1-Administrative File), Folder 4)
  - Louise McNeilly, 1996-1997 (Box 9 (1-Administrative File), Folder 5)
  - Louise McNeilly, 1996-1997 (Box 9 (1-Administrative File), Folder 6)
  - Louise McNeilly - Quick Books (3.5 inch floppy), 1996 (Box 9 (1-Administrative File), Folder 7)
  - Louise McNeilly - receipts and invoices, 1996-1997 (Box 9 (1-Administrative File), Folder 8)
  - Louise McNeilly, 1996-1997 (Box 9 (1-Administrative File), Folder 9)
  - Louise McNeilly, 1996-1997 (Box 9 (1-Administrative File), Folder 10)
  - Louise McNeilly, 1996-1997 (Box 9 (1-Administrative File), Folder 11)
  - Louise McNeilly, 1996-1997 (Box 9 (1-Administrative File), Folder 12)
  - Louise McNeilly, 1996-1997 (Box 9 (1-Administrative File), Folder 13)
  - Louise McNeilly, 1996 (Box 9 (1-Administrative File), Folder 14)
  - Louise McNeilly, 1996-1997 (Box 9 (1-Administrative File), Folder 15)
  - Multicultural Committee, 1996-1998 (Box 9 (1-Administrative File), Folder 16)
  - Newsletter Ads, ca.1996 (Box 9 (1-Administrative File), Folder 17)
  - Newsletter Quotes, 1996 (Box 9 (1-Administrative File), Folder 18)
  - Phone Log, 1996 (Box 9 (1-Administrative File), Folder 19)
  - Referral Log, 1996 (Box 9 (1-Administrative File), Folder 20)
  - SEFA, 1996-1997 (Box 9 (1-Administrative File), Folder 21)
  - Tides Foundation, 1996 (Box 9 (1-Administrative File), Folder 22)
  - TrustCo Account - Women's Building Operating Fund - Fiscal Year, 1966-1997 (Box 9 (1-Administrative File), Folder 23)
  - Volunteer List, 1996 (Box 9 (1-Administrative File), Folder 24)
  - Walk Pledges, 1996 (Box 9 (1-Administrative File), Folder 25)
  - Advertising, 1997; Undated (Box 9 (1-Administrative File), Folder 26)
  - Advertising - Alternative Healing, Donna Reynolds, 1997 (Box 9 (1-Administrative File), Folder 27)
  - Art and Desire, ca.1997 (Box 9 (1-Administrative File), Folder 28)
  - Louise McNeilly, 1997 (Box 9 (1-Administrative File), Folder 29)
  - Art and Desire, 1997-1999; Undated (Box 9 (1-Administrative File), Folder 30)
  - Art and Desire, 1997-1999; Undated (Box 9 (1-Administrative File), Folder 31)
  - Art and Desire, 1997-1999; Undated (Box 9 (1-Administrative File), Folder 32)
  - Art and Desire - receipts, 1997-1998 (Box 9 (1-Administrative File), Folder 33)
  - Art and Desire - sale receipts, 1997-1998 (Box 9 (1-Administrative File), Folder 34)
  - Art and Desire - sale receipts, 1997-1998 (Box 9 (1-Administrative File), Folder 35)
  - Art and Desire - sale receipts, 1997-1998 (Box 9 (1-Administrative File), Folder 36)
  - Art and Desire - sale receipts, 1997-1998 (Box 9 (1-Administrative File), Folder 37)
  - Art and Desire - sale receipts, 1997-1998 (Box 9 (1-Administrative File), Folder 38)
  - Combined Federal Campaign, 1997-1998 (Box 9 (1-Administrative File), Folder 39)
  - Coming Into Our Own Campaign, 1997 (Box 9 (1-Administrative File), Folder 40)
  - Committee Lists, 1995-1996 (Box 9 (1-Administrative File), Folder 41)
  - Date Rape Grant Program, 1997-1999 (Box 9 (1-Administrative File), Folder 42)
  - Deposit Records - TrustCo, January, 1997 (Box 9 (1-Administrative File), Folder 43)
  - Deposit Records - TrustCo, February, 1997 (Box 9 (1-Administrative File), Folder 44)
  - Deposit Records - TrustCo, March, 1998 (Box 9 (1-Administrative File), Folder 45)
  - Deposit Records - TrustCo, April, 1999 (Box 9 (1-Administrative File), Folder 46)
  - Deposit Records - TrustCo, May, 2000 (Box 9 (1-Administrative File), Folder 47)
  - Deposit Records - TrustCo, June, 2001 (Box 9 (1-Administrative File), Folder 48)
  - Gail Dieter - Treasurer Records, 1997-1998 (Box 9 (1-Administrative File), Folder 49)
  - Donations - SEFA, 1997-1998 (Box 9 (1-Administrative File), Folder 50)
  - Grant - Community Foundation, 1997 (Box 9 (1-Administrative File), Folder 51)
  - Grant - Community Foundation or Reel Visions Film Festivals, 1997-1998 (Box 9 (1-Administrative File), Folder 52)
  - Income Tax - Allison Chiropractic, 1997-1998 (Box 9 (1-Administrative File), Folder 53)
  - Issues and Action Committee - notes, 1997 (Box 9 (1-Administrative File), Folder 54)
  - Major Donors, 1997 (Box 9 (1-Administrative File), Folder 55)
  - Marketing, 1997; Undated (Box 9 (1-Administrative File), Folder 56)
  - Louise McNeilly - Be Proud, 1997 (Box 9 (1-Administrative File), Folder 57)
  - Louise McNeilly, 1997 (Box 9 (1-Administrative File), Folder 58)
  - Louise McNeilly, 1997 (Box 9 (1-Administrative File), Folder 59)
  - Membership Efforts, 1997-1998 (Box 9 (1-Administrative File), Folder 60)
  - Non-Profit Financial Management Conference, 1997 (Box 10 (1-Administrative File), Folder 1)
  - Non-Profit Financial Management Conference, 1997 (Box 10 (1-Administrative File), Folder 2)
  - Renaissance/ Volunteers, 1997 (Box 10 (1-Administrative File), Folder 3)
  - Retreat, 1997 (Box 10 (1-Administrative File), Folder 4)
  - Kathleen Rutherford, 1997 (Box 10 (1-Administrative File), Folder 5)
  - Sales Tax Stuff, 1997-1998 (Box 10 (1-Administrative File), Folder 6)
  - SEFA, 1997 (Box 10 (1-Administrative File), Folder 7)
  - United Way, 1997 (Box 10 (1-Administrative File), Folder 8)
  - 403B Stuff, ca.1998 (Box 10 (1-Administrative File), Folder 9)
  - Art and Desire, 1998 (Box 10 (1-Administrative File), Folder 10)
  - Art and Desire, Be Proud, 1998 (Box 10 (1-Administrative File), Folder 11)
  - Bank Statements (TrustCo), 1998-1999 (Box 10 (1-Administrative File), Folder 12)
  - Bills, 1998 (Box 10 (1-Administrative File), Folder 13)
  - Bills Paid, 1998-1999 (Box 10 (1-Administrative File), Folder 14)
  - Checkbooks (blank), ca.1998 (Box 10 (1-Administrative File), Folder 15)
  - Checkbooks (blank), ca.1998 (Box 10 (1-Administrative File), Folder 16)
  - SEFA - Combined Federal Campaign, 1998 (Box 10 (1-Administrative File), Folder 17)
  - Coordinating Council Meeting Minutes, 1998-1999 (Box 10 (1-Administrative File), Folder 18)
  - Winnie DeLoayza - " Holiday Matching Gift ", 1998 (Box 10 (1-Administrative File), Folder 19)
  - Fire Alarm Inspection Report, 1998 (Box 10 (1-Administrative File), Folder 20)
  - Grant - Community Foundation, 1998 (Box 10 (1-Administrative File), Folder 21)
  - Grants Guide, 1998 (Box 10 (1-Administrative File), Folder 22)
  - Holding Our Own Agreement, 1998 (Box 10 (1-Administrative File), Folder 23)
  - Phone List, 1998 (Box 10 (1-Administrative File), Folder 24)
  - Resumes, 1998 (Box 10 (1-Administrative File), Folder 25)
  - Retreat, 1998 (Box 10 (1-Administrative File), Folder 26)
  - Tax Deposit, 1998 (Box 10 (1-Administrative File), Folder 27)
  - Albany Cash Register, 1999 (Box 10 (1-Administrative File), Folder 28)
  - Bank Statements (TrustCo), 1999 (Box 10 (1-Administrative File), Folder 29)
  - Loose Notes, 1999; Undated (Box 10 (1-Administrative File), Folder 30)
  - Newsletter, 1999 (Box 10 (1-Administrative File), Folder 31)
  - Volunteer, 1999 (Box 10 (1-Administrative File), Folder 32)
  - Administrative Resources, 2000 (Box 10 (1-Administrative File), Folder 33)
  - Political Contributions, 2000 (Box 10 (1-Administrative File), Folder 34)
  - Advertising, Undated (Box 10 (1-Administrative File), Folder 35)
  - Capital Campaign Pledges, Undated (Box 10 (1-Administrative File), Folder 36)
  - Checkbooks (blank), Undated (Box 10 (1-Administrative File), Folder 37)
  - Grant Award - The Community Foundation for the Capital Region, Undated (Box 10 (1-Administrative File), Folder 38)
  - Graphics, Undated (Box 10 (1-Administrative File), Folder 39)
  - Health Series Evaluation Sheet (blank), Undated (Box 10 (1-Administrative File), Folder 40)
  - Key Bank Security Deposit Accounts, Undated (Box 10 (1-Administrative File), Folder 41)
  - Media List, Undated (Box 10 (1-Administrative File), Folder 42)
  - Needs Assessment, Undated (Box 10 (1-Administrative File), Folder 43)
  - Letterpress, Undated (Box 10 (1-Administrative File), Folder 44)
  - Membership, Undated (Box 10 (1-Administrative File), Folder 45)
  - " Mistress" Sheet for Posters, Undated (Box 10 (1-Administrative File), Folder 46)
  - Nominating Committee, Undated (Box 10 (1-Administrative File), Folder 47)
  - Notebook, Undated (Box 10 (1-Administrative File), Folder 48)
  - Notebook, Undated (Box 10 (1-Administrative File), Folder 49)
  - Notebook, Undated (Box 10 (1-Administrative File), Folder 50)
  - Notebook, Undated (Box 10 (1-Administrative File), Folder 51)
  - Notebook, Undated (Box 10 (1-Administrative File), Folder 52)
  - Notebook, Undated (Box 10 (1-Administrative File), Folder 53)
  - Notepad, Undated (Box 10 (1-Administrative File), Folder 54)
  - Past Advertisers, Undated (Box 10 (1-Administrative File), Folder 55)
  - Past Evaluation Sheets, Undated (Box 10 (1-Administrative File), Folder 56)
  - Poster Proofs, Undated (Box 10 (1-Administrative File), Folder 57)
  - NSL - Questionnaire, Undated (Box 10 (1-Administrative File), Folder 58)
  - Registration Lists, Undated (Box 10 (1-Administrative File), Folder 59)
  - Resumes, Undated (Box 10 (1-Administrative File), Folder 60)
  - SEFA - Community Works, Undated (Box 10 (1-Administrative File), Folder 61)
  - SEFA - fliers, Undated (Box 10 (1-Administrative File), Folder 62)
  - Senior Aide Position, Undated (Box 10 (1-Administrative File), Folder 63)
  - Women's Building Herstory, Undated (Box 10 (1-Administrative File), Folder 64)
- Programming, 1973-2000, Undated; 2; 4 cubic ft.
  The Programs series includes fliers, promotional material, handouts, schedules, for programs and events that were produced or supported by the Tri-City Women's Center or the Women's Building.
  - Self-Defense Skills, 1973-1983; Undated (Box 1 (2-Programming), Folder 1)
  - Song Lyrics, ca. 1974 (Box 1 (2-Programming), Folder 2)
  - Susan Saxe, 1976 (Box 1 (2-Programming), Folder 3)
  - National Women's Meeting, 1977 (Box 1 (2-Programming), Folder 4)
  - New York State Women's Meeting, 1977 (Box 1 (2-Programming), Folder 5)
  - Potential Programs, 1977; 1979; 1980 (Box 1 (2-Programming), Folder 6)
  - State Now Media, Task Force, ca. 1977 (Box 1 (2-Programming), Folder 7)
  - Unfiled Programs, 1977; 1980; 1981; Undated (Box 1 (2-Programming), Folder 8)
  - Benefit Dinner, 1980 May (Box 1 (2-Programming), Folder 9)
  - Bisexuality Group, 1980 (Box 1 (2-Programming), Folder 10)
  - Health Series Evaluation Sheets, 1980; Undated (Box 1 (2-Programming), Folder 11)
  - Program Schedule, 1981 (Box 1 (2-Programming), Folder 12)
  - Program Task Force Policies Before 1985, ca. 1980 (Box 1 (2-Programming), Folder 13)
  - Career Planning Workshops, 1981; Undated (Box 1 (2-Programming), Folder 14)
  - Programming-Artists Information, 1981; 1982; 1983 (Box 1 (2-Programming), Folder 15)
  - Women's Day, 1981 (Box 1 (2-Programming), Folder 16)
  - Women's Day in the Park, 1981 (Box 1 (2-Programming), Folder 17)
  - Women's Day in the Park, 1981; 1982; 1983 (Box 1 (2-Programming), Folder 18)
  - Women's Day in the Park, 1981; 1985 (Box 1 (2-Programming), Folder 19)
  - Film Series, 1982-1983 (Box 1 (2-Programming), Folder 20)
  - Public Relations- Planning Ahead, 1982 (Box 1 (2-Programming), Folder 21)
  - Women's Day in the Park, 1982 (Box 1 (2-Programming), Folder 22)
  - Take Back the Night, 1983 March (Box 1 (2-Programming), Folder 23)
  - Arts and Entertainment, 1984; 1987; 1988; 1989 (Box 1 (2-Programming), Folder 24)
  - Child Care, 1994 (Box 1 (2-Programming), Folder 25)
  - Dances, 1984 (Box 1 (2-Programming), Folder 26)
  - New England Women's Musical Musical Retreat, 1984; 1987; Undated (Box 1 (2-Programming), Folder 27)
  - Food, 1985 (Box 1 (2-Programming), Folder 28)
  - Legal Clinics, 1985; 1986 (Box 1 (2-Programming), Folder 29)
  - Program Flyers, 1985-1990; Undated (Box 1 (2-Programming), Folder 30)
  - Program Policy Guidelines, 1985 (Box 1 (2-Programming), Folder 31)
  - Program Space Outside Women's Building, 1985; Undated (Box 1 (2-Programming), Folder 32)
  - Women and Business, 1985 (Box 1 (2-Programming), Folder 33)
  - Women Right History, 1985 (Box 1 (2-Programming), Folder 34)
  - Book Discussions, 1986-1987 (Box 1 (2-Programming), Folder 35)
  - Event Flyers, 1986-1989 (Box 1 (2-Programming), Folder 36)
  - Grants for Programming Funding, 1986 (Box 1 (2-Programming), Folder 37)
  - Health, 1986; 1988; 1989 (Box 1 (2-Programming), Folder 38)
  - Ice Cream Social, 1986 (Box 1 (2-Programming), Folder 39)
  - No Limits for Women, 1986 January 22 (Box 1 (2-Programming), Folder 40)
  - Programming Procedures, ca. 1986 (Box 1 (2-Programming), Folder 41)
  - Program Task Force Policies Before 1985, 1986; 1990; 1991; Undated (Box 1 (2-Programming), Folder 42)
  - Senior's- Lecture/ Discussion Series, 1986; 1987 (Box 1 (2-Programming), Folder 43)
  - Women's Caucus for Art, 1986 (Box 1 (2-Programming), Folder 44)
  - Abusive Relationship, 1987; 1988 (Box 1 (2-Programming), Folder 45)
  - AIDS- Related Program, 1987; 1988; 1989; Undated (Box 1 (2-Programming), Folder 46)
  - Co-Sponsored Events Hourly Rental Form, ca. 1987 (Box 1 (2-Programming), Folder 47)
  - Co-Sponsored Programs, 1987 (Box 1 (2-Programming), Folder 48)
  - Communication for Change Workshop (Working with the Media), 1987 (Box 1 (2-Programming), Folder 49)
  - Feminist Spirituality Workshop (Cherokee), 1987 (Box 1 (2-Programming), Folder 50)
  - Feminist Story- Activity Hour, 1987; 1988 (Box 1 (2-Programming), Folder 51)
  - Film and Video Services, 1987; 1988 (Box 1 (2-Programming), Folder 52)
  - Issues of Racism, 1987; 1988; 1989 (Box 2 (2-Programming), Folder 1)
  - National Women's History Month, 1987; 1988 (Box 2 (2-Programming), Folder 2)
  - Networking Fair Mailing List, 1987; 1988; 1989 (Box 2 (2-Programming), Folder 3)
  - Public Speaking, Judi Harris, 1987 (Box 2 (2-Programming), Folder 4)
  - Self-Esteem Workshop, Margie Woods, 1987 (Box 2 (2-Programming), Folder 5)
  - Women's Building Structure, ca. 1987 (Box 2 (2-Programming), Folder 6)
  - Women Under Apartheid- Potluck with Companera Project and Kitchen Table, 1987 (Box 2 (2-Programming), Folder 7)
  - Divora Zipkin - Stress Management Workshops, 1987; 1988 (Box 2 (2-Programming), Folder 8)
  - Anti-Racism/Classism, 1988; Undated (Box 2 (2-Programming), Folder 9)
  - Auction, 1988 February (Box 2 (2-Programming), Folder 10)
  - Building Power For Peace aqnd Justice" - Article for Program Task Force Heads, 1988 (Box 2 (2-Programming), Folder 11)
  - Completed Attendence at Events, 1988; Undated (Box 2 (2-Programming), Folder 12)
  - Completed Programs Forms, 1988 (Box 2 (2-Programming), Folder 13)
  - Consciousness Raising Type Workshops, 1988; Undated (Box 2 (2-Programming), Folder 14)
  - Eating Disorder Workshop, 1988; Undated (Box 2 (2-Programming), Folder 15)
  - Financial Planning, 1988; 1989 (Box 2 (2-Programming), Folder 16)
  - Women's Building Flyers - For Flyer Notebook, 1988; 1990; 1991; 1992; Undated (Box 2 (2-Programming), Folder 17)
  - Forms From Past Events, Space renters only, 1988 (Box 2 (2-Programming), Folder 18)
  - Free to Be All You Can Be, 1988 (Box 2 (2-Programming), Folder 19)
  - Honoring the Feminine Principle: Native American Traditions, 1988 (Box 2 (2-Programming), Folder 20)
  - International Women's Day Celebrations, 1988 March 8 (Box 2 (2-Programming), Folder 21)
  - International Women's Issues, 1988 (Box 2 (2-Programming), Folder 22)
  - The Knowledge Collection, 1988 (Box 2 (2-Programming), Folder 23)
  - Lesbian Workshops, 1988 (Box 2 (2-Programming), Folder 24)
  - Lobby Day, 1988 (Box 2 (2-Programming), Folder 25)
  - Mothers, Children, Youth, 1988; 1989 (Box 2 (2-Programming), Folder 26)
  - Mythology and Race, 1988 (Box 2 (2-Programming), Folder 27)
  - Louise McNeilly - Auctions, 1988; 1991; 1993; 1997; 1999 (Box 2 (2-Programming), Folder 28)
  - Planning Sheets for Women's Building Progress, 1988 (Box 2 (2-Programming), Folder 29)
  - Programming Survey - Completed Forms, 1988 (Box 2 (2-Programming), Folder 30)
  - Programming Task Force, 1988 (Box 2 (2-Programming), Folder 31)
  - Programming Task Force, 1988 (Box 2 (2-Programming), Folder 32)
  - Program Task Force Guidelines after January 1988 restructuring (Box 2 (2-Programming), Folder 33)
  - Program Task Force - Letter about the Women's Building purpose and activities, 1988 March (Box 2 (2-Programming), Folder 34)
  - Program Task Force - Twenty frequently asked questions about the Women's Building, ca. 1988 (Box 2 (2-Programming), Folder 35)
  - Margaret Weinland - Stress Workshops, 1988; 1989 (Box 2 (2-Programming), Folder 36)
  - Program Task Force - Women's Building History/Purpose, 1988 (Box 2 (2-Programming), Folder 37)
  - Recipes for Ritual, ca. 1988 (Box 2 (2-Programming), Folder 38)
  - Social Events, 1988 (Box 2 (2-Programming), Folder 39)
  - Solstice Events, 1988 (Box 2 (2-Programming), Folder 40)
  - Spirituality/Seasonal, 1988 (Box 2 (2-Programming), Folder 41)
  - Video Series, 1988 (Box 2 (2-Programming), Folder 42)
  - Women and Disabilities, 1988 (Box 2 (2-Programming), Folder 43)